Nahaliel Bioni Alves da Silva

Maringá, Paraná, Brazil Phone: <u>+55 (48) 9 9910-6484</u>

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/nahaliel-bioni
Email: nbioni.developer@gmail.com/nahaliel-bioni
Github: github.com/Nbioni

Sitrius. gittius.com//vk

SUMMARY

As a dedicated and professional software developer with nine years of experience in various programming stacks, I am committed to providing innovative and efficient technological solutions. My strengths include being attentive, observant, creative, authentic, and communicative. I'm always excited about growing my skills, learning, and contributing to the success of international technology companies.

EDUCATION

- Executive MBA in I.T. Management, IPOG
- Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering, Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Goiás - February 2019.

SKILLS

- Desktop Development: Flutter, C#, Delphi 7, VB6
- Web Development: Flutter, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, ASP.NET, Angular + TS, VueJS
- Mobile Development: Flutter, React Native, Angular + TS
- Backend: C#, NodeJS, NestJS
- B.I.: Qlik Sense

EXPERIENCE

- Software Engineer Codelitt Miami, Florida, USA - Remote May 2022 - February 2023
 - Developed a modular Flutter project using clean architecture and an Atomic Design System.
 - o Built a Chrome extension using the Design System in Flutter
 - o Maintained a web solution in VueJS
- Sênior Developer/Tech Lead Trinus Tech Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil - Remote June 2021 - May 2022
 - Led a team in developing a backend solution in NestJS with Prisma ORM and a website in Flutter
 - o Implemented Clean Architecture patterns and the <u>Flutter Modular</u> architecture made by the <u>Flutterando community</u>

Software Engineer - K2 Improving Performance

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil - Remote

November 2020 - January 2021

Developed management and payment solutions using .NET

Sênior Developer - TOCTEC

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

February 2020 - May 2020

o Developed plugins for the BIM tool, web systems, and mobile applications (Flutter) for civil construction

Full-Stack Developer - Lidere Soluções

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

October 2019 - February 2020

o Worked on Front-end, Sketch modeling in Adobe X.D., and application development in React Native

Full-Stack Developer - Rede Frota

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

June 2019 - September 2019

- Developed web solutions using Angular + TypeScript
- Developed backend solutions using C#

IT Analyst - InfinIT Tecnologia

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

October 2018 - June 2019

- o Developed .NET C# system
- Developed mobile projects in ReactJS
- o Conducted monitoring BI consultancies with Qlik Sense

Internship - Tribunal de Contas do Estado de Goiás

Goiânia, Goiás, Brazil

November 2016 - October 2018

- Developed .NET solutions in C# using layered architecture, MVC, and Oracle PL/ SQL database
- Worked on maintenance of legacy systems in VB6

Internship - Secretaria Cidadã

Goiânia. Goiás. Brazil - Remote

February 2014 - January 2016

- o Developed Delphi 7 system
- o Worked on SQL Server database, system control, and sending payments for the "Renda Cidadã" and the "Projeto Pão e Leite" of the State of Goiás.